Microsoft   B-COMPANY
has   O
announced   O
the   O
release   O
of   O
a   O
beta   O
version   O
of   O
the   O
popular   O
TensorFlow   O
machine   O
learning   O
library   O

Apple   B-COMPANY
has   O
launched   O
the   O
release   O
of   O
a   O
beta   O
version   O
of   O
the   O
popular   O
TensorFlow   O
machine   O
learning   O
library   O

The   O
London   B-PLACE
metro   I-PLACE
will   O
soon   O
enter   O
the   O
21st   O
century,   O
ditching   O
single-use   O
paper   O
tickets   O
for   O
rechargeable   O
electronic   O
cards   O

The   O
Indian   B-PLACE
metro   I-PLACE
is   O
going   O
to   O
enter   O
the   O
21st   O
century,   O
ditching   O
single-use   O
paper   O
tickets   O
for   O
rechargeable   O
electronic   O
cards   O